Guide to the Centerbrook Architects and Planners Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Project records, Circa 1963-2004
  - Cedar Rapids Museum of Arts, 1984
    - Presentation Drawings (Box G1, Box G10, Box G36)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box G35, Box G40, Box G43–G46)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box G39)
    - Photographs (Box G10)
    - Slides (Box G10)
    - Negatives (Box G10)
  - Chester Diversified Properties, 1972
    Job location: Chester, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box N3)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box N6)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box N3)
    - Photographs (Box N3)
  - Church Street South Redevelopment, 1972
    - Manuscript Materials (Box C1, Box A23)
    - Sketches (Folder A13)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box F1, Folder A11, Folder A14)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box A18–A20)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box E74)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box B7, Box A12, Box A17–A18, Folder A7–A10, Folder A13)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box A17, Folder A7, Folder A10)
    - Photographs (Box B6)
    - Slides (Box F27, Folder A15)
    - Negatives (Box A25–A26)
  - Citizens Federal Savings and Loan, 1963
    Job location: San Francisco, CA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box N3)
    - Photographs (Box N3)
    - Slides (Box N3)
  - Clark House, 1971
    Job location: Old Lyme, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box N2)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box N7)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box N7)
    - Photographs (Box N2)
    - Slides (Box N2)
  - Clocktower, 1986-1987
    Job location: Middletown, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box L1–L6)
    - Sketches (Box L7, Box L9)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box L8–L9)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box L16)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box L10, Box L12–L15)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box L11)
    - Photographs (Box L5)
    - Slides (Box L5)
  - Colby College Student Center, 1986
    Job location: Waterville, ME
    - Manuscript Materials (Box F11–F23)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box F73, Box F76)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box F71)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box F70)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box F72, Box F74–F75)
    - Photographs (Box F11)
    - Slides (Box F11)
  - Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory: Airslie, 1975
    Job location: Cold Spring Harbor, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box D1)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box D15)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box G1, Box P13)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box D15)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box D15)
    - Slides (Box D1)
  - Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory: Grace Auditorium, 1986
    - Manuscript Materials (Box H7–H10)
    - Sketches (Box H8–H9, Box H12)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box H12, Box H16)
    - As-Built/Record Drawings (Box H18)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box H12)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box H11, Box H13–H15, Box H17)
    - Photographs (Box H10)
    - Slides (Box H10)
  - Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory: Jones Laboratory, 1976
    - Manuscript Materials (Box D1)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box D7)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box P13)
    - Slides (Box D1)
  - Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory: Neuroscience Center, 1986-1991
    - Manuscript Materials (Box P26–P36)
    - Sketches (Box P14, Box P22)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box P15, Box P22–P24)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box P18)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box P1, Box P13)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box P16–P17, Box P19, Box P25)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box P19–P21)
    - Photographs (Box P36)
    - Slides (Box P36)
  - Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory: Sammis Hall, 1978-1981
    - Manuscript Materials (Box P4)
    - Sketches (Box P38)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box P1)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box P37)
    - Photographs (Box P4)
  - Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory: Waste Water Treatment Plant, 1976
    - Manuscript Materials (Box D1)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box D17–D18)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box G1)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box D17–D18)
    - Slides (Box D1)
  - Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory: Chancellor's House, "Watson House", 1994
    - Manuscript Materials (Box R30)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box R1)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box R29)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box R1)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box R1)
    - Photographs (Box R32)
    - Slides (Box R32)
  - Consulate General's House
    - Presentation Drawings (Box E75)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box C14)
  - Cook House (unbuilt), 1979
    Job location: Great Falls, VA
    - Sketches (Box E24, Box E26–E27)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box E25)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box E24, Box E26, Box E28, Box E31)
    - Slides (Box E15)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box E24, Box E27–E30)
  - Cornuelle House, 1965-1966
    - Presentation Drawings (Box B8)
  - County Federal Savings Bank, 1973
    Job location: Greens Farms, Westport, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box C1)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box C57)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box C56–C57)
    - Photographs (Box C1–C2)
    - Negatives (Box C1)
  - Court Street Center, 1985
    Job location: Cincinnati, OH
    - Manuscript Materials (Box G14)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box G49)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box G49–G50)
    - Photographs (Box G14)
    - Slides (Box G14)
  - Cranbury Road Housing, 1975
    Job location: Hightstown, NJ
    - Manuscript Materials (Box N3)
    - Sketches (Box N3)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box N8)
  - Crowell House I, 1975
    Job location: Vermont
    - Manuscript Materials (Box D1)
    - Slides (Box D1)
  - Dartmouth College: Hood Museum of Art, 1981-1985
    Job location: Hanover, NH
    - Manuscript Materials (Box Q1–Q4)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box Q24)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box Q25)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box Q23)
    - Photographs (Box Q2)
    - Slides (Box Q2)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box Q16–Q17, Box Q21–Q22)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box Q18–Q20)
  - Dartmouth College: Tuck School of Business - Chase House renovation, 1993
    - Manuscript Materials (Box R34, Box R46)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box R34)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box R28)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box R28)
  - Dartmouth College: Tuck School of Business - Byrne Hall, Dining and Classroom Building, 1993
    - Manuscript Materials (Box R34–R45)
    - Sketches (Box R10)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box R11, Box R13–R19, Box R34)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box R7, Box R12, Box R20–R21)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box R7–R9, Box R34, Folder R47)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box R20–R21, Box R24)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box R22–R23)
    - Photographs (Box R34)
    - Slides (Box R34)
    - Negatives (Box R34)
  - Dartmouth College: Tuck School of Business - Stell Hall renovation, 1993
    - Manuscript Materials (Box R34, Box R46)
    - Sketches (Box R26, Box R28)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box R18, Box R28)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box R24, Box R26)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box R26, Box R28)
    - Photographs (Box R34)
    - Slides (Box R34)
    - Negatives (Box R34)
  - Dartmouth College: Tuck School of Business - Dormitory
    - Manuscript Materials (Box R34–R45)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box R34)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box R25, Box R34, Folder R47)
    - Slides (Box R36)
    - Negatives (Box R36)
  - Dartmouth College: Tuck School of Business - Murdough Hall renovation, 1993
    - Manuscript Materials (Box R34–R45)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box R27)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box R27)
  - Dauntless Yacht Club, 1972
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box F63)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box F63)
  - Dayton Kiwanis Floating Fountain, 1978
    Job location: Dayton, OH
    - Manuscript Materials (Box K4)
    - Sketches (Box K4)
    - Slides (Box K4)
  - Dayton Riverdesign, 1977
    - Manuscript Materials (Box J4–J5, Box S59)
    - Sketches (Box J4–J5)
    - Photographs (Box J4–J6)
    - Slides (Box J4–J5)
    - Negatives (Box J4–J5)
    - Audiovisual Materials (Box J4–J5, Box J60)
  - Dayton Riverfront Park, 1978
    - Manuscript Materials (Box K4)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box K7)
    - Photographs (Box K4)
    - Slides (Box K4)
  - East Hampton Library and Multicultural Center, 1986
    Job location: East Hampton, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box F25–F26, Box F29)
    - Sketches (Box F32, Box F40–F42)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box F37–F38, Box F46–F47)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box F33–F34)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box F35–F36, Box F39)
    - Photographs (Box F25–F26, Box F29)
    - Slides (Box F29)
  - East Lyme Library and Community Center, 1986-1990
    Job location: East Lyme, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box P57–P65A)
    - Sketches (Box P52)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box P39–P44)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box P39)
    - As-Built/Record Drawings (Box P44–P47, Box P50–P52, Box P55)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box P41)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box P47–P49, Box P53–P56)
    - Photographs (Box P65)
    - Slides (Box P65)
  - Eastern Kentucky Housing Development Corporation
    Job location: Whitesburg, KY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box B12)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box B10)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box B9)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box B9)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box B9)
    - Photographs (Box B11, Box E55)
  - Eisenstein House, 1993
    Job location: Fayette, MO
    - Manuscript Materials (Box R31)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box R5)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box R29, Box R31)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box R5–R6)
    - Photographs (Box R33)
    - Slides (Box R33)
  - Eisenstein House II - Barn & Studio addition, 1998
    - Manuscript Materials (Box R31)
  - Eisenstein House - Library renovation, 2003
    - Manuscript Materials (Box R31)
  - Eisenstein House III - Pool, Storage Building, Site Improvements, 2007
    - Manuscript Materials (Box R32–R33)
  - Elliott - Gruen House, 1982
    Job location: Ligonier, PA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box E64)
    - Sketches (Box E68)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box E67–E68)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box E65–E66)
    - Photographs (Box E64)
    - Slides (Box E64)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box E67)
  - Elmwood Park Revitalization, 1983
    Job location: Roanoke, VA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box K8)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box M13)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box K9–K10)
    - Slides (Box K8)
  - Encosystems Spec House, 1974
    - Manuscript Materials (Box K4)
    - Sketches (Box K4, Box K11)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box K11)
  - Essex Point, 1969-1972
    Job location: Deep River, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box N3)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box N9–N10)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box N11)
    - Photographs (Box N3)
  - Farber House renovation, 1974
    Job location: Woodbridge, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box N3)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box N6)
    - Photographs (Box N3)
  - Fremont City Hall Competition, 1965
    Job location: Fremont, CA
    - Sketches (Box L1)
    - Negatives (Box L1)
  - Gagarin House
    Job location: Peru, VT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box B12)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box B13)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box B14)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box B13)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box B13)
  - Gazebo for House & Garden, 1969
    - Manuscript Materials (Box B12)
    - Sketches (Box B15)
    - Photographs (Box B12)
  - Goodman House, 1969
    Job location: Montauk, NY
    - Sketches (Box B16–B17)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box B16–B18)
  - Grace Auditorium, Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory, 1986
    - Presentation Drawings (Box Q36)
  - Gringer Apartment, 1989
    - Manuscript Materials (Box M2)
    - Sketches (Box M6)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box M7)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box M8)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box M7)
    - Photographs (Box M2)
    - Slides (Box M2)
  - Gross House, 1970
    Job location: Hartland, VT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box N4)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box N4, Box N13)
    - Photographs (Box N4)
  - Guest House in the Country, 2003-2004
    Job location: Connecticut
    - Manuscript Materials (Box Q15)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box Q45)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box Q45)
    - Photographs (Box Q15)
  - Gund Investment Corporation Offices, Phases I and II, 1982
    Job location: Princeton, NJ
    - Manuscript Materials (Box J19)
    - Sketches (Box J7–J9, Box J13–J15)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box J10–J18)
    - As-Built/Record Drawings (Box J16–J18)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box J15, Box J19)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box J13–J18)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box J7–J9)
    - Photographs (Box J19)
    - Slides (Box J19)
  - Halprin House, 1966
    Job location: Sea Ranch, CA
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box B19)
    - Slides (Box B12)
  - Harrison House, 1966
    Job location: Santa Barbara, CA
    - Sketches (Box B20)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box B20)
  - Heritage Harbor, 1971
    Job location: Annapolis, MD
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box C17)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box C16–C18)
    - Photographs (Box C1)
    - Negatives (Box C2)
  - Hindman Pool, 1972
    Job location: New Zion, KY
    - Presentation Drawings (Box N12)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box N12)
  - Hines House, 1968
    - Manuscript Materials (Box N3)
    - Sketches (Box N3)
    - Photographs (Box N3)
  - House Beautiful House [see also Burlington House #292], 1983
    Job location: Burlington, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box K5, Box E32)
    - Sketches (Box E33B–E33C)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box E33B, Box E35)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box E33A)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box E33C)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box E33A, Box E34, Box E36)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box E33C)
    - Photographs (Box E32)
    - Slides (Box E32)
  - House in the Country, 1992
    - Manuscript Materials (Box Q5)
    - Sketches (Box Q27)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box Q27)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box Q28, Box Q36)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box Q26)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box Q26)
    - Photographs (Box Q5)
    - Slides (Box Q5)
  - Hubbard House, 1961
    Job location: Corral de Tierra, CA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box N2)
    - Sketches (Box N2)
    - Photographs (Box N2)
  - Huntington Station Plaza, 1969-1975
    Job location: Huntington, NY
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box B21–B22, Box B25)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box B25)
    - As-Built/Record Drawings (Box B23)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box B21, Box B25)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box B25)
    - Photographs (Box C2, Box B24)
    - Slides (Box B24)
  - Indian Springs Ranch, 1973
    Job location: Salinas, CA
    - Presentation Drawings (Box N13, Box F60)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box F60–F62)
  - Ingenium, 1992-1993
    - Manuscript Materials (Box Q12)
    - Sketches (Box Q39)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box Q39)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box Q39)
  - Ireland House, 1970
    Job location: Chilmark, Martha's Vineyard, MA
    - Presentation Drawings (Box N12)
  - Isham House, 1977
    Job location: Sagaponack, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box D6)
    - Sketches (Box D6)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box D9, Box F30)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box D10)
    - Photographs (Box D6)
    - Slides (Box D6)
  - Jaffe House II/ House on the Connecticut Seashore, 1986-1991
    - Manuscript Materials (Box P66)
    - Sketches (Box P68, Box P70)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box P69, Box P72)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box P67, Box P73)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box P69)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box P67, Box P70–P71, Box P73)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box P67, Box P73)
    - Photographs (Box P66)
    - Slides (Box P66)
  - Jaffe House II Pool Trellis, 2000
    - Manuscript Materials (Box P66)
    - Sketches (Box P74)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box P74)
    - Slides (Box P66)
  - Jewell House, 1963
    Job location: Orinda, CA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box N2)
    - Sketches (Box N2)
    - Photographs (Box N2)
    - Slides (Box N2)
  - Jobson House, 1961-1963
    Job location: Palo Colorado Canyon, CA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box D3, Box B12)
    - Sketches (Box D3)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box D24)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box D24, Box B26)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box D24)
    - Photographs (Box F1, Box D3, Box B12)
    - Slides (Box D3)
  - Johnson House, CA, 1965
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box D28)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box D28)
  - Johnson House, NY, 1978; 1988
    Job location: Canaan, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box D3, Box N13)
    - Sketches (Box D3)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box N13)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box D28)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box D28)
    - Photographs (Box D3)
    - Slides (Box D3)
  - Jones House Additions and Renovations, 1982
    Job location: Stamford, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box E32)
    - Sketches (Box E69)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box E69)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box E70)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box E69)
    - Slides (Box E32)
  - Kansas City Urban Graphics, 1973
    Job location: Kansas City, MO
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box F59)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box F59)
    - Photographs (Box F27)
  - Kaplan House, 1983
    - Manuscript Materials (Box E1)
    - Sketches (Box E37)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box E37)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box E37)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box E37)
    - Slides (Box E1)
  - Karas House, 1966
    Job location: Monterey, CA
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box B27)
    - Photographs (Box B12)
    - Slides (Box B12)
  - Kingsmill on the James Housing, 1973-1974
    Job location: Williamsburg, VA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box C1, Box K5)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box F1, Box C62–C63)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Folder F2)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box C15, Box C62)
    - Photographs (Box C1)
    - Negatives (Box K5, Box E55)
  - Kissam House Addition
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box B28)
  - Klotz Development, 1971
    Job location: West Hampton, NY
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box F30)
  - Klotz House, 1970
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box B29)
    - Photographs (Box B24)
  - Klugman House, 1979
    - Manuscript Materials (Box E38)
    - Sketches (Box K12, Box E39)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box E39–E40)
    - Photographs (Box E38)
  - Knisely I Vacation House, 1978
    Job location: New York
    - Manuscript Materials (Box D3)
    - Sketches (Box D3)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box D23)
    - Photographs (Box D3)
    - Slides (Box D3)
  - Knisely II House, 1988
    - Manuscript Materials (Box D3)
    - Sketches (Box D3)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box D11)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box D11, Box D21)
    - Photographs (Box D3)
    - Slides (Box D3)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box D11, Box D20)
  - Koizim House, 1969-1973
    Job location: Westport, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box C25, Box C39)
    - Sketches (Box C38)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box C38)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box C25, Box C38–C39)
    - Photographs (Box C2–C3)
    - Slides (Box C1)
    - Negatives (Box C2, Box E55)
  - Krementz Studio, 1989-1990
    - Manuscript Materials (Box P95)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box P94)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box P94)
    - Photographs (Box P95)
  - Kuhio Shores Mauka, 1975
    Job location: Kauai, HI
    - Manuscript Materials (Box N2)
    - Photographs (Box N2)
  - Lawrence House, 1966
    - Manuscript Materials (Box N2)
    - Sketches (Box N2)
    - Photographs (Box N2)
    - Slides (Box N2)
  - Lawrence University: Wriston Art Center, 1989
    Job location: Appleton, WI
    - Manuscript Materials (Box K12, Box K25–K30)
    - Sketches (Box K16–K18)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box K13, Box K15, Box K19–K20)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box K24)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box K14–K15, Box K20–K22)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box K23)
    - Photographs (Box K12, Box K30)
    - Slides (Box K30)
    - Negatives (Box K30)
  - Lenz Winery, 1982
    Job location: Peconic, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box F24)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box F56)
    - Presentation Drawings (Folder F3)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box F57)
    - Photographs (Box F24)
    - Slides (Box F24)
    - Sketches (Box F57–F58)
  - Les Halles Competition, 1979
    Job location: Paris, France
    - Manuscript Materials (Box E32)
    - Sketches (Box E41A–E41B)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box E41A–E41B)
    - As-Built/Record Drawings (Box E41A–E41B)
    - Photographs (Box E32)
  - Levin House, 1971-1974
    Job location: Little Falls, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box K4)
    - Sketches (Box M13)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box K31)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box M13)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box K32)
  - Lone Hill Housing, 1964
    Job location: San Jose, CA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box N2)
  - "Long View", 1987-1994
    Job location: "New England"
    - Manuscript Materials (Box P87–P93)
    - Sketches (Box P75, Box P82–P83, Box P86)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box P75, Box P77, Box P82, Box P86)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box P81)
    - As-Built/Record Drawings (Box P76, Box P85)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box P78)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box P76, Box P78, Box P80, Box P84)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box P79)
    - Photographs (Box P93)
    - Slides (Box P93)
  - Lovejoy Fountain, 1968
    Job location: Portland, OR
    - Manuscript Materials (Box K5)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box K6)
    - Photographs (Box K5–K6)
    - Slides (Box K5)
  - Malibu Apartments, 1972
    Job location: Malibu, CA
    - Presentation Drawings (Box I2)
  - Manville Apartment / Friday Apartment, 1985-1988
    - Manuscript Materials (Box F4–F10)
    - Sketches (Box F50–F51, Box F53–F55)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box F48–F50)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box F51–F55)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box F50–F52)
    - Photographs (Box F4)
    - Slides (Box F4)
  - Maplewood Terrace Low-Income Housing, 1978
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box B31)
    - Slides (Box B32)
    - Negatives (Box B33)
  - "Marsh Estate", 1987-1991
    Job location: "East Coast"
    - Manuscript Materials (Box P137–P159)
    - Sketches (Box P112, Box P121)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box P110–P111, Box P113–P115, Box P119, Box P127, Box P131–P133)